More2game 隱私政策 Privacy policy
=============================

* * *

### 隱私政策

我們不會收集及以任何形式儲存來自你社交網路的任何資訊或銷售給廣告或其它營運機構。

### 個人信息

當你透過社交網路進行分享時，可能會要求輸入帳號密碼，但該資訊由iOS系統管理，App不會以任何形式儲存帳號密碼，也不會收集及以任何形式儲存您在社交網路上的任何個人資訊。

### 隱私政策條款

使用本App即表示您同意此隱私政策的條款和條件。如果您不同意本政策，請不要使用該App。我們保留權利，在我們決定更改，修改，增加或刪除本政策的部分，在任何時候。請定期瀏覽此網頁查閱任何修改。如果您繼續使用我們的App以後的任何更改這些條款的發布將意味著你已經接受了這些調整。

為了實現分享和推送功能，我們使用了MobTech的ShareSDK和Mobpush產品，此產品的隱私策略條款，可以參考：[http://www.mob.com/about/policy](http://www.mob.com/about/policy)

連絡信箱: kefu@more2.cn

### 您的權利

我們會盡力維護個人信息的準確和完整，並及時進行更新，前提是您應確保提交的所有個人信息都準確無誤。

#### 1、個人信息的訪問、更新和刪除；

（1）您有權訪問我們持有的關於您的特定的個人信息；  
（2）您有權要求我們更新您或更正您的不准確的個人信息；  
（3）改變您授權同意的範圍；  
（4）您有權要求我們刪除您的個人信息。  
您可以通過您可以通過應用內設置界面-反饋-聯繫客服，或郵箱kefu@more2.cn聯繫我們，我們會在15個工作日內答复您的請求。為保護您的隱私，申請時需填具申請文件，並提交可資確認身份之證明文件，若未提供或有提供不實之情形以致於無法確認您的真實身份，我們將無法受理您的請求。若委託他人代為申請者，應出具委任書，並提供本人及代理人可資確認之身份證明文件。

#### 2、您可以選擇是否披露信息

有些信息是使用本公司服務所必需的，但大多數其他信息的提供決定權由您掌握。您可以通過刪除信息、關閉設備功能方式改變您授權我們繼續收集信息的範圍或撤回您的授權。

#### 3、聯繫與諮詢

在訪問、更正、更新、改變和刪除前述信息時，我們可能會要求您進行身份驗證，以保障信息安全。如您需要，您可以通過FB粉絲頁或者郵箱（kefu@more2.cn）聯繫遊戲客服進行操作。我們會在合理的期限內答复您的請求。同時請您理解，由於技術所限、法律或監管要求，如果我們有合理依據認為這些請求存在欺騙性、無法實行或損害他人隱私權，我們則會拒絕處理請求。

### Facebook資訊蒐集以及移除須知

（1）用戶使用Facebook授權登入應用程序，我們會蒐集使用者的電子郵箱和個人公開資料，主要用於創建帳號和提供個性化服務。

（2）用戶刪除遊戲應用程序 或 在Facebook設定和隱私移除應用授權，我們會刪除使用者的全部資訊。

（3）用戶如後續不再使用Facebook授權登入，可以聯繫我們進行應用程序的Facebook授權數據內容資訊刪除，一經刪除將無法恢復。

* * *

### PRIVACY POLICY

We do not collect and save from your social account in any form or sell any information to advertisers or other operators.

### Personal information

When you share information through social accounts may be asked to enter the account and password, but that information is management by iOS system. App does not save account and password in any form or collect and save any personal information in any form on your social account.

### Privacy Policy Terms

Use this App mean you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this App. We reserve the right, in our decision to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Publish any changes to these terms if you continue to use our App future will mean that you have accepted these adjustments.

In order to realize the function of pushing messages, we use MobTech's Mobpush product. For the privacy policy terms of this product, please refer to : [http://www.mob.com/about/policy](http://www.mob.com/about/policy)

E-Mail : kefu@more2.cn

### Your rights

You should ensure that all personal information submitted is accurate and update it in a timely manner. We will try our best to maintain the accuracy and completeness of personal information.

#### 1\. Access, update, and deletion of personal information;

(1) You have the right to access the specific personal information we hold about you;  
(2) You have the right to request us to update or correct your inaccurate personal information;  
(3) Change the scope of your authorization;  
(4) You have the right to request us to delete your personal information.

You can use the in-app settings interface-feedback-contact customer service, or email kefu@more2.cn to contact us, and we will respond to your request within 15 working days. In order to protect your privacy, you need to fill in the application documents when you apply, and submit the identification documents that can be used to confirm your identity. If you do not provide or provide false information so that your true identity cannot be confirmed, we will not be able to accept your request. . If you entrust others to apply for the application, you should issue a letter of appointment and provide identification documents that can be confirmed by you and your agent.

#### 2\. You can choose whether to disclose information

Some information is necessary to use the company's services, but most other information is provided by you. You can change the scope of your authorization to continue to collect information or withdraw your authorization by deleting the information and turning off the device function.

#### 3\. Contact and consultation

When accessing, correcting, updating, changing, and deleting the aforementioned information, we may require you to verify your identity to ensure information security. If you need, you can contact the game customer service through the FB fan page or email (kefu@more2.cn) to operate. We will respond to your request within a reasonable time limit. At the same time, please understand that due to technical limitations, legal or regulatory requirements, if we have a reasonable basis to believe that these requests are deceptive, unfulfillable, or damage the privacy of others, we will refuse to process the request.

### Facebook Information Collection and Removal Instructions

(1) When the user logs in to the app with Facebook authorization, we will collect the user's email address and personal public information, which are mainly used to create an account and provide personalized services.

(2) If the user deletes the game application or removes the application authorization in Facebook settings and privacy, we will delete all the user's information.

(3) If the user no longer uses Facebook authorization to log in, he can contact us to delete the Facebook authorization data content information of the application. Once deleted, it will not be restored.

* * *

### More2gameプライバシーポリシー

本プライバシーポリシーは、More2game及び、その運営の関連会社（以下「当社」といいます）が運営するゲームサービス（以下「本サービス」といいます）、ウェブサイト、及び関連するサービスを利用するにあたり利用者に適用されます。また、本サービスにおいて利用者から取得した利用情報は、本プライバシーポリシーに従い管理されます。当社は、利用者のプライバシー保護を我々に課された社会的責務と認識し、最優先に考えています。利用者に当社のサービスを安心してご利用いただくため、以下の基本方針に基づき、利用情報の取扱いに万全を期して参ります。

#### 1．利用者情報について

ここでいう利用者情報とは、その情報に含まれるニックネーム、またはゲーム内で利用者別に付けられた番号などにより容易にその利用者を特定できる情報を指します

#### 2\. 利用情報について

当社は、利用情報の収集目的を明確に定め、目的達成に必要な限度で利用情報を収集します。また、各サービスで情報を収集する際は、利用目的を明示し利用者の同意を得るようにします。この際、利用者はご自分の意思で手続きを進めるかどうか決めることができます。ただし、利用情報について利用者が提供を望まれない場合には、当社が提供するサービスの一部をご利用いただけなくなる場合があります。

#### 3\. 利用情報の利用について

利用情報は予め提示した目的の範囲内でのみ利用いたします。 (1) 当社では、当社がご提供するサービスのコンテンツやサービスの品質向上、新規サービスの開発のため利用状況を統計的に分析することがあります。 (2) 当社では収集した利用情報を市場調査の目的で利用する場合があります。その場合には、利用者を特定する情報は一切掲載または公開しません。 (3) 収集した利用情報を使用して、当社の新サービスのご案内や、興味を持っていただける特別なご案内の提供をさせていただく場合があります。 (4) 収集した利用情報を使用して、利用者に対して当社に対するご意見やご感想（商品及びサービスに対するご意見やご感想を含む）のご提供をお願いする場合があります。 (5) 利用者にコンタクトする必要が生じた場合には、ニックネーム、電子メールアドレス等を利用してご連絡させていただく場合があります。 (6)マーケティングや販売促進のため、利用者を識別できない統計データを作成し、新規サービスの開発業務のために利用することがあります。 当社は、個人情報を第三者に譲渡することはいたしません。本サービスを利用者にとってより効果的なものとする目的以外で、利用情報を使用する場合には、予め当該サービスの公式サイト等でその目的を公表するものとします。

#### 4.利用情報の第三者への開示について

当社は、以下のいずれかに該当する場合を除き、原則として利用者の利用情報を第三者に対して開示、漏洩または提供することはいたしません。 (1) 利用者本人の同意を得た場合。 (2) 人の生命、身体、財産の保護のために必要がある場合であって、利用者本人の同意を得ることが困難である場合。 (3) 国の機関もしくは地方公共団体またはその委託を受けた者が法令の定める事務を遂行することに対して協力する必要がある場合であって、利用者本人の同意を得ることにより当該事務の遂行に支障を及ぼすおそれがある場合。 (4) その他の法令により開示又は提供が許容されている場合。 (5) 利用情報を提供した利用者本人から明示的に第三者への開示または提供を求められた場合。 (6) 当社の営業の全部または一部を第三者に譲渡し、当社を吸収合併または当社と新設合併し、あるいは分社化する場合で、当社から営業譲渡を受けた第三者、当社を吸収合併した会社または新設合併により設立された会社、あるいは分社した会社に譲渡する場合。 (7) その他利用者へのサービス提供のために必要であると当社が合理的に判断し、利用者に事前の同意の上、開示する場合。

#### 5\. 利用情報の編集について

利用者は一度入力した情報（携帯番号、メールアドレスなど）を二度と変更することはできないものとします．

#### 6.国際間送信について

当社は利用情報を国境を越えて、関連会社に転送する事ができ、皆様が属する法域から別の法域に移転する場合がある事にご同意頂きます。

#### 7\. プライバシーポリシーの変更

当社は、法改正や事業内容の変更、利用者の要望等により、本プライバシーポリシーの内容を改善・改定する事があります。このプライバシーポリシーを、いつでも、事前の予告なく、かつ特段の理由なくして変更する権利を有します。重要な変更がある場合には、告知することといたします。

#### 8.その他

当社は、ご利用者様の個人情報の取扱いに関係する法令その他の規範を遵守するとともに、プライバシーポリシーの内容を継続的に見直し、改善に努めます。 当サイトの個人情報についてのご質問・その他お問い合わせは、弊社お問い合わせページ、または下記よりご連絡ください

9.プッシュ通知機能を実現するため、弊社はMobTechのMobpushというサービスを使用することに決定いたしました。当該サービスのプライバシーなどの詳細についてはこちらのウェブサイトでご確認ください　 [http://www.mob.com/about/policy](http://www.mob.com/about/policy)

#### 【お問い合わせ】

E-Mail : kefu@more2.cn

### お客様の権利

当社は全力を尽くして個人情報の正確さと完備を維持し、適時に更新します。ただし提出した個人情報はすべて正確で間違いないように確保してください。

#### 1、個人情報のアクセス、更新、削除；

（1）お客様は当社が所有している特定の個人情報にアクセスすることができます。  
（2）お客様は個人情報の更新や修正を要求することができます。  
（3）お客様が承認した範囲の変更ができます。  
（4）お客様は個人情報の削除を要求することができます。

アプリ内設定インターフェース-フィードバック-カスタマーサービスに連絡するか、kefu @ more2.cnにメールでお問い合わせください。15営業日以内にリクエストに返信します。 プライバシーを保護するため、申請時に申請書類に記入し、本人確認に使用できる身分証明書を提出する必要があります。本人確認ができないように虚偽の情報を提供または提供しない場合は、ご要望はお受けできません。 他の人に申請者の代理を任せる場合は、任命状を発行し、その人と代理人が確認できる身分証明書を提出する必要があります。

#### 2、情報の承認

当社のサービスを利用するためにお客様の承認が必要です。情報の提供決定権はお客様にあります。情報を削除したり、デバイスの機能をオフにしたりすることによって、情報収集の範囲を変更したり、ライセンス（承認）を撤回したりすることができます。

#### 3、連絡と相談

上記の情報をアクセス、訂正、更新、変更、削除する際には、情報の安全を保障するため、お客様の個人情報の提供を求められる場合があります。必要な場合、FBファンページまたはメールアドレス（kefu@more2.cn）に連絡してください。当社は合理的な期限内にお客様の要請に答えます。同時に、技術の制限及び法律や監督管理に基づき、お客様の要求は偽情報、欺瞞があり、実行できない、または他人のプライバシーを損なうと判断する場合、お客様の処理要求を拒否とします

厦门魔兔网络科技有限公司

icp信息：闽B2-20160110

_

_

地址：厦门民族路50号世纪中心9层   电话：0592-5153993
